A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Educational Interests, Series G FA316
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Donald McLean's File - India International House
  - 1959 (Box 136, Folder 1050)
  - 1960-1962 (Box 136, Folder 1051)
  - 1962-1964, 1966 (Box 136, Folder 1052)